hi you're on the Air Ken I was wondering
how you would think that it would be
possible to regulate the sale of these
guns and want to know if you
suck I have one last thing to say okay
um can you like strip nak danc like a
I'm a big fan of Harley riding cuz I
love how it vibrates my testicles and I
like to jack off and
mastbate hello car you're on the air oh
yeah I would really like to ramp you in
the right now look at
you look at you struggling look at you
look at you you fing piece of
sh that was some truly hilarious hate
speech you pranksters those were what's
known as public access call-in shows and
the reason they look so old is because
they are nowadays we just tweet mean
things at people who are on TV it's no
secret that I think Nick Sabin is a
horrible human and it doesn't help that
he just hired that whiny arrogant
Beautiful Lane kein so imagine my
delight when I found out lane and his
lovely wife have a public access
[Music]
show welcome back you're on Triple K
what's your question hey Lane just
wondering if it's natural Talent or if
you guys practice fumbling all the
time you stupid piece of all
right I'm going to go jizz inside your
of a
wife all right no pain no Lane next
caller I love what youve done to open up
the offense and give the tight and
identity as a passing team and uh I was
wondering what Nick sa's oatmeal cream
pies taste like when he HS them in your
mouth youing coward War Eagle you
you
look maybe we uh start screening some of
these calls I'd like to apologize to our
viewers second down let's try again long
time caller firsttime listener big USC
fan I hope you dive AIDS you overpaid
we have got to get a longer cord
next season who am I kidding we're not
going to be here next year next caller
what was it like being the last
regretting Al Davis's 50-year career
full of fuckups I'll take your answer
off the air you licking sh for
brains two-part question now that you're
down south you going to divorce your
wife so you can start farm
animals and if you do divorce your wife
you think she'll be able to handle my
big fat Co after all those years your
pencil dick when are you going to be
head coach again sweetie not now my love
next caller oh nice trophy case you un
winning look how goddamn empty that
thing is where you going to fail upward
next I got a question about the huddle
offense okay this one I should be able
to handle why do you think you prefer to
hurry up but every time I your
smoking hot wife in the ass she begs me
to slow down I'm pretty sure that was
Urban Meyer next caller are you going to
be the next coordinator to start
molesting children just kidding I know
you are you face pedophile
people really don't like you next caller
Bama fans are all sister
God damn it I hope you all die in a next
caller and keep it clean and don't say a
word about my wife nice tits nice
do oh yeah look at you hit the hit the
oh yeah oh yeah that's going to work
idiot I don't know how it
work hey do you wear that visor when you
your
dad I can't wait to see one of you show
up to college game day with a sign that
says kein Crimson corner you
[Music]
Hillbillies